<Document>
  #Monolith Rules

  ##Foreword

  Servers are often a diluted mess of rules and restrictions that hinder players' creative abilities and freedom to craft their own experiences.

  Our vision is centered on empowering players to handle most, if not all, situations independently.

  Remember, [bold]this is just a game; nothing more[/bold]. We understand that it is often impossible to follow every rule to the letter at all times. We all make mistakes.

  We do expect, at the very least, that you [bold]stay in-character, adhere to the setting, and engage in quality roleplay to the best of your abilities[/bold].

  This ensures your enjoyment and enhances the experience for the other players around you.

  [color=red]If any of the links do not work, use the guidebook version on the escape or (Numpad 0) menus.[/color]

  [color=red]These rules are expected to be read in their entirety.[/color]

  ##Admin Decisions
  - All admin decisions are final.
  - Rules are enforced to the spirit of the rules and subject to admin interpretation.
  - Admins may disregard any/all rules if they deem it in the best interest of the current round, the server, and/or the community.
  - Admins are accountable for their actions. Abuse of admin privileges will be dealt with by staff.

  ##General Information
  - Disconnecting from or ignoring/evading admin-helps will result in an appeal-only ban.
  - Admins are not obligated to cover player losses, deaths or delays.
  -- This includes, but is not limited to: ship deeds, money, respawns and revivals.
  -- Any action taken is at the staff's discretion, and depends on the circumstances.

  # Rule List

  All of the below rules apply at all times, including between rounds, in-game and elsewhere in our community.

  ## Core Rules
  These are the core rules of Monolith.
  - 1. [textlink="Use common sense." link="MonolithRuleOneCommonSense"]
  - 2. [textlink="Respect each other." link="MonolithRuleTwoRespect"]
  - 3. [textlink="Do not engage in cheating or exploits." link="MonolithRuleThreeCheatingExploits"]
  - 4. [textlink="Do not use alternative accounts." link="MonolithRuleFourAlternativeAccounts"]

  ## Roleplay Rules
  These are the roleplay rules of Monolith.
  - 1. [textlink="Do not break character." link="MonolithRuleFiveBreakCharacter"]
  - 2. [textlink="Avoid misusing in-character text chat." link="MonolithRuleSixTextChat"]
  - 3. [textlink="Type with proper grammar in in-character text chat." link="MonolithRuleSevenProperGrammar"]
  - 4. [textlink="Speak English exclusively in out-of-character situations." link="MonolithRuleEightSpeakEnglish"]
  - 5. [textlink="Build upon the contributions of others." link="MonolithRuleNineCharacterActions"]
  - 6. [textlink="Erotic roleplay is prohibited." link="MonolithRuleTenEroticRoleplay"]
  - 7. [textlink="Do not metagame." link="MonolithRuleElevenMetagame"]

  ## Conflict Rules
  These are the conflict rules of Monolith.
  - 1. [textlink="Avoid random deathmatch." link="MonolithRuleTwelveRandomDeathmatch"]
  - 2. [textlink="Adhere to the new life rule." link="MonolithRuleThirteenNewLife"]
  - 3. [textlink="Engage in fair play when making demands." link="MonolithRuleFourteenFairPlay"]

</Document>
