<Document>
  # JUDICIARY-CLASS E.R.V
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MercenaryTechFab"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponTurretL85Autocannon"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ResearchAndDevelopmentServer"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MachineArtifactAnalyzer"/>
  </Box>
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Medium

  [color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 1-3

  [color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Antimatter Engine (AME)

  [color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] All

  [color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None

  "Judiciary-class Expeditionary Research Vessels are refitted Research hulls from a past era of galactic civil war. They are armed and armored, but are not the best choice for ship-to-ship combat. They instead excel with their manufacturing capability and personnel armament."

  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST

  ## 1. Power supply

  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESAdvanced"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationWallBasic"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the Antimatter Engine (AME) generator is functional (View below.)
  - Check that the SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the substation unit is charging.
  - Check that the Engineering/Research APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check that the Server Room/Atmos APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check that the Bridge APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.

  ## 1.2. Antimatter Engine (AME) reactor unit.
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeController"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeJar"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the AME control device is anchored to the floor and connected to a 3x3 containment shielding structure.
  - Check that the AME control device is connected to the cable terminal of your SMES via HV.
  - Check the fuel remaining of the generator unit.
  - Enable Injection.
  (Note: AMEs automatically generate power equivalent to demand.)

  ## 2. Atmospherics

  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirCanister"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Catwalk"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that both air canisters are anchored to their respective connector ports.
  - Check that outgoing distribution air pump is ON. (This may require removal of covering catwalk with WIRECUTTERS.)

  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirAlarm"/>
  </Box>

  - Enable external waste loop pump. (Located outside of server room.)

  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that both gyroscopes are anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.

  ## Sidenotes

  * - Judiciary-class vessels have an isolated server room contained within a vacuum. In order to access Telecomms, the Gunnery server, or the Research server, EVA is required.


  * - Notably, due to refit specifications, the AME has little armor and is a significant weak spot during combat. However, it is also on the side of the vessel with the most external weapons.


  * - Totaling combined APC wattage can appraise the rough power requirements of the vessel. Base power consumption is approximately 24kw, more if running shields, fabricating, moving or firing weapons.
</Document>
