<Document>
  # Ship Warfare

Warfare on the frontier is usually done via the means of [color=orange]ship gunnery[/color].

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponTurretL85Autocannon"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GunneryServer"/>
  </Box>

There are 3 types of ship weaponry available:
 - [color=gold]Ballistics[/color], which are weapons like autocannons, railguns, and all other unguided chemical-propellant weapons.
 - [color=MediumVioletRed]Energy[/color], which are weapons like plasma weaponry, lasers, and other similar non-chemical based weapons.
 - [color=GreenYellow]Missiles[/color], which are all guided munitions. It explains itself.

Ship weapons all need a [color=orange]gunnery control console[/color] and a [color=slateblue]gunnery control server[/color] to function. They will be abbreviated to [color=orange]GCC[/color] and [color=slateblue]GCS[/color] in most instances.

Ship weapons only fire if they are selected and if your cursor on the [color=orange]GCC[/color] is in the FOV of the turret.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShipMissileASM302"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponTurretVanyk"/>
  </Box>

Missiles will only track grids with a shuttle console, and are immediately pointed towards their tracked target upon firing. Take into account the detection angle of your missiles, you can fire a lot farther than what the FOV of your turrets will allow if you do.

## Shield Generators

Some ships are equipped with [color=cyan]shield generators[/color]. These absorb all incoming impacts, and add power draw for every projectile absorbed. [color=yellow]Note that shields only react to projectiles fired from ship weapons, not regular handheld weapons or tools.[/color] Shields will NOT block beam or hitscan weapons, such as [color=red][bold]lasers[/bold][/color], and the effects of [color=teal][bold]EMPs[/color][/bold] will still go through.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CircularShieldConsole"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CircularShieldBase"/>
  </Box>

Due to the rarity of these, they are unable to be looted, and must be scavenged if you wish to outfit your ship with them. They can be fabricated if you have the suitable T3 arsenal research for it though.
The most popular shield system for example, the [bold][color=cyan]MS-225[/color][/bold], adds power usage based on the damage of projectiles it absorbs, with approximately [bold][color=coral]105w per point of damage[/color][/bold].
After [bold]25 seconds[/bold], this power surge will start to dissipate.
- Above [bold][color=red]1.5mW[/color][/bold], the shield will turn off, and only reenable once under [bold][color=yellow]200kW[/color][/bold] of power usage.

However there is a base power draw, and it is calculated via the following equation.

Radius^2 * Shield Width * 0.5 * Power/m^2.

  ## Bluespace Drives

  Many large, expedition, and combat ships are equipped with a [color=dodgerblue]Bluespace Drive[/color]. These can be fabricated with a T3 experimental research.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MachineFTLDrive"/>
  </Box>

These increase the ship's FTL range by a certain amount if powered. For the [color=dodgerblue][bold]CTLA-25[/bold][/color], this range is [bold]5000m[/bold]

</Document>
